serverpress.com 2016-11-20

# Privacy Policy • ServerPress, LLC.

At ServerPress, LLC., we believe you have a right to know what type of information we may collect when you interact with us and our practices with respect to that information. The guidelines contained herein apply only to information collected by or for ServerPress, LLC. This includes, among other things, websites operated by or for ServerPress, LLC., most of which contain “www.serverpress.com” in their URLs. Sites which are linked to/from these sites (including sites of other ServerPress’s affiliated companies and via banner ads may have different policies; therefore, please review the privacy policy notices on those sites for details.

While ServerPress, LLC. does not generally require that you provide us with personally identifiable information (for example, in order to visit and use the site “www.serverpress.com”), please note that in order to participate in some activities, it will be necessary for you to provide this information. If you choose not to provide it for those activities, you may not be able to participate in them.

[Notice to California Residents – Your California Privacy Rights: If you are a California resident, you have the right to receive: a) information identifying any third party company(ies) to whom ServerPress, LLC. may have disclosed, within the past year, personal information pertaining to you and your family for that company’s direct marketing purposes; and b) a description of the categories of personal information disclosed. To obtain such information, please email your request to [info@ServerPress.com](mailto:info@ServerPress.com).]

### Collection of Information:

For each visitor to the [www.serverpress.com](https://www.serverpress.com/) website, ServerPress’s web server automatically recognizes, collects and/or stores information such as the visitor’s IP address/Domain name combination and any referring sites. ServerPress, LLC. may use several technologies to accomplish this. Examples of such technologies are cookies and web beacons. When you visit ServerPress’s websites or advertisements appearing thereon, or use one or more of the ServerPress’s website services, or receive emails from either the ServerPress.com domain, we may use an industry-wide technology called “cookies” which stores certain information on your computer and which will allow us to customize your experience to better match your interests and preferences or to simply facilitate your signing in to use the services. Most browsers will allow you to erase cookies from your computer hard drive, block acceptance of cookies, or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. However, if you block or erase cookies, we may not be able to restore any preferences or customization settings you previously specified and our ability to personalize your online experience would be limited. Please refer to your browser instructions or “help” screen to learn more about these functions. ServerPress, LLC. may also itself use, or engage third parties to use, web beacons for researching certain usage and activities on our website. The information collected by ServerPress, LLC. or requested from third parties through these web beacons is in an aggregate, non- individually identifiable form and is used to find out more about users including demographic information and usage patterns for more accurate reporting and to improve the effectiveness of our marketing. ServerPress, LLC. may also itself use, or engage third parties to use, pixel tags or other technology to research or track your usage activities with respect to emails from us. ServerPress, LLC. may ask you to provide “personal information”, meaning individually identifiable information such as your email address, name, mailing address, telephone number, social security number, credit card number, or persistent identifier (such as a customer number held in a cookie) which is associated with individually identifiable information, to enable you to participate in contests, chat rooms, on bulletin boards, to fill out a registration, or to order products and services using the site at the domains “ServerPress.com”. ServerPress, LLC. may combine the information you provide on our website(s) with information we may collect offline from you or from third parties so that we can more effectively tailor our site, services and offerings to you.

ServerPress, LLC. will not share the personal information you provide with any other parties, except (a) to other affiliated ServerPress, LLC. companies (i.e., (i) ServerPress, (ii) any company of which 50% or more of its outstanding shares are owned by ServerPress, LLC., directly or indirectly, and (iii) any company with the name ServerPress” as a part of its trade name) who may want to contact you about products, services or other offerings that may be of interest to you, (b) with your consent (see paragraph below), (c) as may be required by law or court order, (d) to persons or companies with whom ServerPress, LLC. engages to carry out or provide support for the operations of the sites or our business, or (e) to appropriate third parties, including law enforcement or other government agencies, in connection with a criminal investigation, fraud prevention, or other legal action or if ServerPress, LLC. reasonably believes it is necessary to do so to protect ServerPress, LLC., its customers, or the public.

Unless you instruct us otherwise, ServerPress, LLC. may contact you to provide information about products, services, promotions, contests, or other activities or offerings that may be of interest to you. You can instruct us whether or not you wish to be contacted by checking or un-checking the box indicating your preference, as applicable, at the place where your information is collected. In addition, with each communication you receive from ServerPress, LLC., you will be given the opportunity to indicate if you do not wish to receive future communications from the company.

You can also to opt out of information related to consumer products by sending a message directly to [info@ServerPress.com](mailto:info@ServerPress.com) with the subject line “Remove Me”.With your consent, ServerPress, LLC. may share your personal information with third parties outside of ServerPress, LLC. who may want to contact you about products, services or other offerings that may be of interest to you. Each of these companies may have their own privacy policies. ServerPress, LLC. will seek to obtain your consent at the place where the information is collected either by an “opt-out” or “opt-in” method, or by other means (such as an email request). If you consent to receiving communications from any of these third parties, you will need to communicate with them directly if you later decide that you no longer wish to receive their communications.

For instructions on how to request changes to the personal information you have provided to ServerPress, LLC., please send an email to: [info@ServerPress.com](mailto:info@ServerPress.com) or write to us at:

ServerPress, LLC.  
931 n 33rd St.  
Milwaukee, WI  53208  
Telephone: (619) 800-8478

Use and Disclosure of Anonymous Aggregated Information  
ServerPress, LLC.may also collect, aggregate and maintain anonymous information about you, such as your hobbies, interests, purchasing habits, music preferences, and the like. This data can then be used to tailor ServerPress’s promotions, advertising, and communications to deliver a better experience for you. ServerPress, LLC. may also share such aggregate information with advertisers, business partners, sponsors, and other third parties; for example, to inform them about the percentage of male/female visitors to our site or the percentage of visitors within a particular age range.

### Security

ServerPress, LLC.takes great care in maintaining the security of your personal information and in preventing unauthorized access to it through the use of appropriate technology and internal procedures. However, ServerPress, LLC. does not guarantee that unauthorized access will never occur.

Notice To/Regarding Children Under the Age of 13  
ServerPress, LLC.believes that children using the Internet require special protection, and we urge parents or guardians to explain Internet safety to their children. Parents are urged to spend time online with their children to become familiar with the types of content available on the ServerPress, LLC. sites and the Internet in general. Control tools are available from online services and software manufacturers to help create a safer environment for children.

If you are under 13 years of age, you should not provide any personally identifiable information (for example, your last name, home address or e-mail address) on these sites without the knowledge and permission of your parent or guardian. If ServerPress, LLC. learns that you are under 13 years of age, ServerPress, LLC. will not maintain or use any personally identifiable information about you without the verifiable consent of your parent or guardian, except as allowed by law. This may mean that you will be unable to participate in some activities on the site without that verifiable consent. If a child under 13 years of age wishes to participate in any ServerPress’s website activity, or wishes to take advantage of a product or service offering available to children, and to do so necessitates the furnishing of any of the child’s personal information, please note the following:

(i) The name, address, telephone number, and email address of the operator collecting or maintaining personal information from children through this website are as follows:

ServerPress, LLC.  
931 n 33rd St.  
Milwaukee, WI  53208  
Telephone: (619) 800-8478  
e-mail address: [info@ServerPress.com](mailto:info@ServerPress.com)

(ii) The types of personal information collected from children may include the name, email address, home address, telephone number and/or any other information reasonably necessary for the child to participate in a particular activity. This information may be collected directly and/or passively (e.g., through a web server that automatically recognizes and stores information such as a visitor’s IP address/domain name combination).

(iii) The information collected may be used for purposes such as fulfillment of a requested transaction, record keeping, marketing back to the child, or making it publicly available through a chat room or by other means.

(iv) Unless specific consent is obtained from the child’s parent or guardian, the child’s personal information will not be disclosed to third parties who are not contractors hired to carry out the internal operations of the websites, other than as may be required or permitted by law. We have required, or will require, such contractors to agree to use personal information of site visitors only for the purposes of carrying out these operations and to keep such information confidential. A parent or guardian has the option of consenting to the collection and use of the child’s personal information without consenting to the disclosure of that information to third parties.

(v) ServerPress, LLC. is prohibited from conditioning a child’s participation in an activity on the child’s disclosing more personal information than is reasonably necessary to participate in such activity; and

(vi) A parent can review and have deleted the child’s personal information, can refuse to permit further collection or use of the child’s information, and can revoke or limit consents previously given.  
Except as permitted by law, before any collection of a child’s personal information takes place at a website directed to children or where ServerPress, LLC. is knowingly collecting children’s personal information, the child will be asked to provide his/her parent’s or guardian’s e-mail address so that ServerPress, LLC. can contact the child’s parent or guardian. ServerPress, LLC. will then send an email (the “Initial Notification”) to the parent/guardian indicating, among other things, the information that the child is requested to provide, the intended use(s) of the information and information on how the parent/guardian can, at their election, delete the child’s information from ServerPress’s database or records. Upon receipt of the Initial Notification, a parent or guardian may respond back to ServerPress, LLC. to grant his/her consent or to deny consent in which case ServerPress, LLC. will delete the parent or guardian’s email address and any other personal information, if any, previously obtained for securing parental consent. Upon ServerPress’s receipt of the parent/guardian consent, ServerPress, LLC. will send a confirming email to the parent/guardian’s email address or take such other action as may be required to verify the consent.

If ServerPress, LLC. desires to use a child’s information for purposes other than that for which the parent/guardian consent was previously given, ServerPress, LLC. will not do so without first getting the parent/guardian consent.  
Consent to Processing:

By providing any personal information to ServerPress’s site(s) including  “www.serverpress.com”, all persons, including without limitation persons in the member states of the European Union, fully understand and unambiguously consent to the collection and processing of such information in the United States of America.

Policy Governs Use: Changes to Privacy Policy  
The terms of this policy will govern the use and any information collected while it is in place. ServerPress, LLC. reserves the right to change this policy at any time, so please re-visit this page as often as you wish.

Questions:  
If you have any questions or comments about our personal information practices or about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to send us an email at [info@ServerPress.com](mailto:info@ServerPress.com) or write us at:

ServerPress, LLC.  
931 n 33rd St.  
Milwaukee, WI  53208
